export const chapter = "Chapter - 11: Preposition";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "What is the primary characteristic of Simple Prepositions?",
          optionA: "They consist of two words.",
          optionB: "They are made up of one word.",
          optionC: "They are always followed by a verb.",
          correctAnswer: "b) They are made up of one word.",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which of the following is an example of a Compound Preposition?",
          optionA: "at",
          optionB: "on",
          optionC: "in addition to",
          correctAnswer: "c) in addition to",
        },
        {
          question:
            'In the sentence "I saw about three monkeys jumping across the canal," what type of preposition is "about"?',
          optionA: "Simple Preposition",
          optionB: "Compound Preposition",
          optionC: "Prepositional Phrase",
          correctAnswer: "b) Compound Preposition",
        },
        {
          question:
            "When can a preposition be placed at the end of a sentence?",
          optionA: "Only in passive sentences",
          optionB: "Only in interrogative sentences",
          optionC:
            "Under specific situations, such as when a relative pronoun is used as the object",
          correctAnswer:
            "c) Under specific situations, such as when a relative pronoun is used as the object",
        },
        {
          question:
            'In the sentence "The popular poet lies deep buried in," what does the preposition "in" indicate?',
          optionA: "Location",
          optionB: "Time",
          optionC: "Purpose",
          correctAnswer: "a) Location",
        },
        {
          question:
            'What type of preposition is used in the phrase "on behalf of"?',
          optionA: "Simple Preposition",
          optionB: "Compound Preposition",
          optionC: "Prepositional Phrase",
          correctAnswer: "c) Prepositional Phrase",
        },
        {
          question:
            'In the sentence "They will come at 7 o\'clock on Monday," what is the preposition and its object?',
          optionA: "Preposition: at, Object: 7 o'clock",
          optionB: "Preposition: on, Object: Monday",
          optionC: "Preposition: at, Object: Monday",
          correctAnswer: "a) Preposition: at, Object: 7 o'clock",
        },
        {
          question: 'Which preposition is attached to the word "abide"?',
          optionA: "in",
          optionB: "by",
          optionC: "from",
          correctAnswer: "b) by",
        },
        {
          question:
            'What does the preposition "over" indicate in the phrase "crow over"?',
          optionA: "Time",
          optionB: "Place",
          optionC: "Position",
          correctAnswer: "c) Position",
        },
        {
          question:
            'In the sentence "This decision was taken in consequence of those circumstances," what type of preposition is "in consequence of"?',
          optionA: "Simple Preposition",
          optionB: "Compound Preposition",
          optionC: "Prepositional Phrase",
          correctAnswer: "c) Prepositional Phrase",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blanks:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question: "The boy was ___________ his studies.",
          optionA: "engaging in",
          optionB: "aspiring for",
          optionC: "absorbed in",
          correctAnswer: "c) absorbed in",
        },
        {
          question: "Women have to be gold to __________ for silver.",
          optionA: "pass off",
          optionB: "cut out",
          optionC: "run over",
          correctAnswer: "a) pass off",
        },
        {
          question: "We should __________ by the school rules.",
          optionA: "abide by",
          optionB: "agree with",
          optionC: "bark at",
          correctAnswer: "a) abide by",
        },
        {
          question: "The officer imposed a fine __________ him.",
          optionA: "for",
          optionB: "on",
          optionC: "after",
          correctAnswer: "b) on",
        },
        {
          question: "The rich must not look down __________ the poor.",
          optionA: "to",
          optionB: "upon",
          optionC: "after",
          correctAnswer: "b) upon",
        },
        {
          question: "A police team was __________ the matter.",
          optionA: "jumping into",
          optionB: "investigating into",
          optionC: "complying of",
          correctAnswer: "b) investigating into",
        },
        {
          question: "We are __________ on the new project.",
          optionA: "crowing over",
          optionB: "embarking on",
          optionC: "coming into",
          correctAnswer: "b) embarking on",
        },
        {
          question: "An old man was __________ by a bus.",
          optionA: "falling off",
          optionB: "run over",
          optionC: "aspiring for",
          correctAnswer: "b) run over",
        },
        {
          question: "Please bear __________ us; it will take a little longer.",
          optionA: "on",
          optionB: "to",
          optionC: "with",
          correctAnswer: "c) with",
        },
        {
          question:
            "This decision was taken in __________ of those circumstances.",
          optionA: "consequence",
          optionB: "lieu",
          optionC: "addition",
          correctAnswer: "a) consequence",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3)
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "An Adverb is a type of speech that adds to the meaning of an Adjective, a Verb, or another Adverb in a sentence.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adverbs of Manner indicate the place where an action is done.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Adverbs of Time show the time when an action is done.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adverbs showing place or direction are usually placed at the beginning of a sentence.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adverbs of Degree indicate the quantity or extent of an action.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Interrogative Adverbs are used to ask questions about the manner in which an action is done.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adverbs showing place or direction should always be placed at the end of a sentence.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "When an Adverb modifies a Transitive Verb, it can be placed between the Verb and its Object.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adverbs of definite frequency are generally placed at the beginning of a sentence.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adverbs of Degree indicate the time when an action is done.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };

export var activityData;
